Nina Gamble

SKILLS

Filmmaking BA graduate with a passion for post production, specifically editing. I have a strong interest in current affairs. I am also interested in the role that social media and the media plays in modern life. Within my work I have focus on queer culture, feminist issues and fashion. This focus takes the form of the experimental genre, however I have also branched into documentary. Having worked in retail and customer based roles since the age of 16 I have a disciplined work ethic, working both independently and within a group setting.

EXPERIENCE

GOE Wellness, London — Video Editor / Social Media Assistant

July 2022 - February 2023

As a video editor my responsibilities include: editing videos for our wellness platform (such as workout routines and meditation guides), producing and publishing content for our social media platforms, and assisting our marketing team in social media strategy. As a social media assistant I supported the marketing team in running social media accounts and solely ran the company TikTok. I would produce, publish and schedule content in line with events and product launches, to bring in a larger audience to the growing company.

Giulio Fashion, London — Customer Assistant

August 2021 - January 2022

During this time I worked closely with individual clients, catering the shopping experience to each one. My role included styling and choosing pieces from the newest luxury brand collections to present, whilst building a strong relationship with each client to learn their likes and dislikes.

Polyesterzine, **London** — Social Media Assistant

October 2020 - November 2020

During this time I worked with PolyesterZine to help them get started using the social media platform TikTok, and carry over the content from other platforms. Within this I edited videos, planned content uploads and reviewed what was getting the most engagement on TikTok.

EDUCATION

Kingston School of Art, Kingston — Filmmaking BA

September 2019 - May 2022

During my filmmaking degree at Kingston School of art I have developed skills in all aspects of the filmmaking process from pre production to post production. Taking on varying roles across my three years of studies I gained a specific interest in the editing process and began to take professional focus on this role within my projects. I aim to start a career allowing me to hone in on the pre production skills I have developed and grow professionally. I also gained massive experience in sound recording including interviews and foley which helped me in my editing and sound

showreel: https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=yL60HebLoQk&ab channel=NinaGamble

SKILLS

- -Competent with Microsoft Office and Apple MAC software
- -Competent with Adobe Premiere pro and Audition
- -Competent with varied sound recording equipment and procedures
- -Competent with social media backend navigation and planning